Friends, welcome here to your own
Stock Market Investor Pro. I hope
you all are friends. This
video is going to be very unique.
Very few people know about this city
and about their business.
Many people know the name but they do business.
It is not clear to many people.
Therefore, the two shares of ICICI Bank of the
same group are very good and very
profitable. There is tremendous momentum in it. But I will
not see any moment in it, but use something like this. You will
see tremendous momentum in it
in the coming time. So if you have
this, then what should you do after that,
you know that there is a lot of activity going on in the market.
Exams of many companies are being conducted, so
many companies are getting your bonus. News of
ABP News is also included, like when I am a
factor of two-three companies, then Reliance
Reliance, you may get a bonus on that,
Wipro, after that Infosys, two-three
companies, after the exam,
you may get the bonus in your account here. There is no
vacant seat for the user. But
this is news. It may happen in the coming time.
Send it correctly. The range is that game
in force has also reached.  VIP Road has been reached
and Reliance has reached, it has reached 543
shares, you can see a tremendous rise in it
in the coming time that the bonus can be
destroyed, so this does not mean that there is a hundred percent
guarantee of it, here
only this product is mentioned that yes, it can be available on it
because that is the same thing that when you
see the registry, whatever you
tell about its performance, I will
make this in a separate video on Twitter,
but here in the video there is going to be a video about
two tremendous fundamentals and board
approved of ICICI, so it is going to be a
very tremendous video,
so find the entire video on this website,
if you are on the channel, then definitely subscribe to my channel
and press together so
that you get notification updates,
I had already uploaded a video in the morning in
which you should participate in the
government's announcement to privatize the PSU banks,
for that and it is
making laddus, which is Atal in the bill,
let's first talk about the company, let's take a look at it, whether
Professor Raj
is the cream of
ICICI Lombard General Insurance  Let's
talk about it, you will get
to see this recipe
in the name of ICICI, so one day now
we have concluded after this, it is giving 98% and a
very good effect, Mithila, there is a decline for you to see in this, so if we
talk about one month, then take about two percent in the stock,
one cannot have much confidence,
one year's fast, one time search
normal, if someone means tremendous, means multi
Agarwal will not keep coming, but
I will tell you some parameters, it is possible that
in the coming time you will have much better coordination, there are
chances of Jasmine, if we talk about 5 years,
it has given very good returns,
that 20% vitamin hair magnet benefits, it is a
lot of time, the company listed in 2017, the
company has not even completed 5 years, the
stock has not performed as well, here the
syrup of one learner is very big that
you are not seeing the decline, it is
definitely moving slowly in only one train, but
you are seeing only one trend, there was a
decline after Kuber, when will it get much more
that the decline would have been taken out from it, here it is 14
years, so that  But it could never be imposed,
₹400 fall was introduced
from English and copy, so a lot of it was presented,
its to win 211 to request to
backup which is pizza bread, breaking it and
going to the store, so once pay
attention here, earlier whatever
support was made for it, it has made it practical,
now the support which is being made here is
making 15, so ₹15 every I tried to touch here,
you tried, ₹15 I
also went up in a bus, I also went up
and went to coaching but
pressed vastu tips top in the market, then I did it, if we
talk about this then the company Brunei
is of 1026, so at this time after understanding this I am giving
you a chance to join it, that is, the
stock which used to
free you in the range of 1415, that is, if
you want to buy a bike, then it is of ₹14 100, if you
get more of 14 in the network behind this time, then give a tremendous
like  Because it is going to have a lot of sons
and I will explain why so
let's also look at the stock of the other one so let's
see this, let's
talk about the sources that launch the company,
it means the companies apk file tamil
actors first and the decision is the company, let's
talk about its value, the valuation of inch is quite
visible but not that much
and the company is not drinking on
Friday, behind the sector, this is visible,
office NPA is visible,
if I did not say citric acid present, everything can be seen to
run, click on this company
profile, you will give,
when do you work with the company, general insurance,
which is private sector, life insurance,
which is less, the channel through which it works in it,
your curse, what does general insurance
mean, now I will explain it in detail,
Begum, and on that sir, it is not a matter, the
revenue of the company seems to be increasing very strongly
and the profit of the company also
seems to be increasing very well, so the company is very good, if
we see any problem in it,
then let us see, only
outside companies were authorized for less than 2021
that  1620, which is that
you will see ₹12, 100 verification
on this, but the intention is, but here
in which state, if you look here today, there is an amazing
delivery, free porn
delivery inside you, let's
talk about information, so here we can see
Sirauli Patrick share holding pattern,
quite a great saver mode was seen,
51.10 modification is getting
intimate company, quite a great your 18
send them different styles that in 2019,
twice the companies are dividend in 2018, first the
company gives sorry dividend and and now let's talk about the
episode app by applying finance,
but that officer, you know that the
fans are quite good if you have got it in this way, if there is
no company from it, it is a good thing
with the company, then this group approved
Life Insurance Corporation Limited
saw a lot of night, whereas
you will see that responsible for more than four percent, there has been a
rise of that point,
if after a month, there is
quite a great Friday in the premises  is getting a
rise of nine percent, if we talk about the stock in 101 years, it has
given a great return of
42%, a very strong cold ride, which life
insurance company has given a good return
after 5 years, then in five years, a tough 350-500
rupees company Kohli Maz, so the company in 2016,
right now the parcel company is
not even ours, the company which is a little oily,
now it has been going up and down, but the company
Ultimate is going up, so here the
company is giving you an opportunity, the company will
give you a tremendous scientific look here, that
means profit booking on it goes in this company,
but the company puts the next hi on it,
then after that it makes zero entry
and all the life insurance companies which you
want go up, see, in the
coming time you will see even more rise here, we will
compare both,
before that let's see other things as well,
friends, this is the fact that this fundamental
company is our lot, Loris is the first company and
along with that its value has also increased a little, see
in calibration, but it cannot increase further right now,
that Bigg Boss's 27385, but its  I am very
excited behind the 3080 area, there are very good song question
ratings, I have set a target to do bike, if we
talk about the way I work with this, then
whose joint venture is this, it is of ICICI Bank and
Sports Live Stock Holding Limited, it is a
joint venture, both work for life
insurance, pension, health insurance,
individual group,
if we talk about its computer superintendent
is Bajaj Finserv, it is from Izzat Sewing Water,
behind it is its competitor Max Life Insurance,
after this the revenue review of 2019 was
seen of Office Don, but
in 2013 it seems to be doing very well and a
little profit of the company seems to be decreasing,
but there are some things that will take it to a very high level,
16 Socrates' disciple brother Sadho, computer is a
holiday today, there is a reason behind it, I will
tell you this and people are only 40, professor 2%
guava, then the police will also
see the speed here in the days of the company, but it is
not necessary right now, this is a trick, it has time only,
if we talk about it, still the percentage
went quite good at around 36  St. Paul, take the
company for information, we will talk to see
Differ company, June 16th is the accident date,
so you have already got tablets for the year, if you
get the fair once in 2019, then
Differ twice in 2019, Differ in 2018 or the company
Differ has given a very good performance in 2021, let's
talk about the Sirody pattern, then
objectively, next they have got that
75% promoters have you
know vitamin, this company is going to rise a lot,
if we talk about its promoters, there is no
grease, no shares are mortgaged,
so this and Rifat, let's look at the back, it is a
long time that Bigg Boss
gave eight no presentations in 3 months, but if we
talk about the crying feature,
you lost 40% on an important point, Shahrukh Aamir
's long afternoon, but you touched one, let's
talk about 40 percent of St.'s in a year
and long gave yourself to the
organization at the level, let's talk about 5 years,
in 5 years you got a lot of phone calls, Angry Birds
number  Net 123 means if we talk in long term, it has
given good returns but
in comparison to this, it has given a little less
return but if we talk about the market then
tell me, it is a long market, you have seen
cheap minutes less,
only their but in this way it is long, it is
quite good against long, there is a pang in the heart of salvation, if we
talk about this then we can stop and make it long,
but you can see the
compression of both is the same, both are great, let me
tell you one more thing, I
told you that general insurance and like
insurance is not covered in it,
in general insurance, and fast auto parts,
morning property, and
if there is insurance but excluding medical etc.,
which means live coverage on this
portal, whatever and there insurance
comes in that general insurance, so both the
companies know this, if we talk here,
now see, if you want general insurance, it
means gift in January
and the processor which you get,
like, comment, you mean SBI
Life Insurance District, under this you have
my and I mean yours, which are different, these two, this,
which is without body, this is a different unique type  If you keep
this in mind, then Ramesh account
has the number on it, you can play Arora ji,
you can take this and it is
also going to give very good returns in the long term,
after the movie Rockstar, how Dedicated
Security has subscribed to this channel,
talk about Motilal Oswal, it has
given the target of euthanasia and this
recording and six members of
Hina, which are being said to be very targeted computers,
if you see after that, the
company has given high vision and bonus,
you will get this bonus, this share, after the bonus,
how much bonus has been given to the policy holder, it is of
867 crores *, then at that
time the company is growing well, then it is
delivering such a tremendous performance, so
both these companies are just the beginning, now is the opportunity,
you need to do the biodata,
if you want to go to the 11th, remember, you should
like it till whatever level, I
am in
Ayodhya, I give, Raksha, once a week the
stock saw a one-sided rise,
after the fall the stock is
not making any support level, if you are doing a
basic in a complete viral, then this hair means only once, then
it saw a fall, so here  But it has gone
tremendously,
you will definitely see a slight decline once, the
area is tied like Chohatan,
then the high profile, which means after this, a
lot of 600 has been sent, I will go up to
600 plus, start, after this it will press a
little and will definitely come to 650, so
whenever you get a chance, it is below the limits, while the
stock comes, you can invest the first installment on it once,
650 really pays the loan till 550
and six super, this Rose Day stock is
very high, it is a similar meaning, it can
go very easily, if you
want, you should play this stock for long term, you can go
tremendously, the stock is very hunter tremendous
and this is a good group, it does
not go in support here,
so if you want to talk about these two, then you can talk and go, it is
very tremendous in the long term,
after a few minutes, the final year of backwards,
whatever you find, you want to talk about your financial
balance,
actual complaint or not, you have to do it by
washing these, whatever I liked,
I told you, after looking at the fundamentals of my shopping company, then you will get it
Sugar Tak This
Birthday Ke